(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-29T10:21:06.488338",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
[Attention: Notice to Attendees]
アニメにハマって
Getting hooked on anime
歌いたくなっちゃった
and wanting to sing along,
推しのシーン見ながらカラオケ歌えるなんて…
being able to sing karaoke while watching your favorite scenes...
尊すぎてつらいっ！
is too precious to handle!
歌いたい曲見つけよう！
Find the songs you want to sing!
どアニメ宣言！
Do Anime Sengen!
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention / 演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください / 声出し応援OKです
[Attention: Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance. Cheering loudly is OK.]
本日は、桃鈴ねねファーストライブ
Thank you very much for attending today's
「花咲くねねねねねねね超会歌」にご来場いただき、ありがとうございます！
Momosuzu Nene 1st Live "Hanasaku Nene Choukaika"!
最後までライブを安心していただくために、いくつかご案内をさせていただきます。
To ensure you can safely enjoy the live concert until the end, we have a few announcements.
ほうりこーだね、みんな。(笑)
Everyone's getting all worked up. (Laughs)
公演中の撮影、録音、録画機材の使用は固くお断りしております。
The use of recording, audio, and video equipment during the performance is strictly prohibited.
館内は禁煙となっておりますので、喫煙はご遠慮ください。すぱすぱ禁止です！
The venue is non-smoking, so please refrain from smoking. Smoking is strictly prohibited!
そして、万が一具合が悪くなってしまった場合は、無理をせずに近くのスタッフへお知らせください。
Furthermore, if you happen to feel unwell, please don't push yourself and notify nearby staff.
会場内での、モッシュ、ダイブ、大きく飛び跳ねる、ステージに物を投げ込むなど、他のみんなの迷惑になったり、公演を妨げる行為は一切禁止とさせていただきます。
Also, moshing, diving, jumping high, throwing objects onto the stage, or disrupting the performance are strictly prohibited.
でも、みんなに飛んでほしいところもあるから、そこはともに、ルールを守って盛り上がっていきましょう！
However, there are parts where we want everyone to jump, so let's follow the rules and get hyped together!
そして、演出の都合上、通路に荷物を置いたり、足をださないようにしてください。これとっても重要です。
Also, for production reasons, please do not place luggage in the aisles or stick your feet out. This is very important.
もしからしたら、あの、荷物とか足がなくなっちゃうおそれがあるので、ちゃんと収納しといてください。
If you don't, your luggage or feet might disappear, so please make sure to store them away properly.
また、本公演は映像配信および写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、客席が映り込む場合がございます。映像や写真はプロモーション等に使用される可能性がありますので、あらかじめご容赦ください。
Also, cameras for streaming and photography will be present, and audience seats may be captured for promotions, so please understand in advance.
また、ライブのハッシュタグは、#ねね超会歌 です！
Also, the official live hashtag is #NeneChoKaika!
トレンド1位ありがとう！
Thank you for trending #1!
まだまだハッシュタグを使ってたくさん盛り上げてね！
Keep using the hashtag to hype it up even more!
それでは、開演までもう少しです！みんなで一緒に盛り上がりましょう！ももすずねねでした！
Well then, we're just moments away from the start! Let's get excited together! This has been Momosuzu Nene!
ハッピーギラファ〜！！
Happy Girafa~!
ねねちのギラギラファンミーティングへようこそ！！
Welcome to Nenechi's Glare-Glare Fan Meeting!!
さぁ！ツノと頬をなで〜く伸ばして
Now! Stretch out your horns and cheeks~
お思いっきり、楽しんじゃおうね！
Let's enjoy it to the fullest!
それじゃあ、いっくよ〜！
Here we go~!
アミーを！カキロ！
Cast amii! Kakiro!
ビバ！ギラファ！
Viva! Girafa!
カブクワ (Hey!!)
Kabukuwa (Hey!!)
ギラギラ最高だね カブクワ
Glare-glare is the best, kabukuwa!
クリクリおめめラブ カブクワ
Round eyes love, kabukuwa!
愛の(ふ！！)ダンスはムートチョ ムートチョ
Love's dance is mu-to-cho mu-to-cho,
飛んで(ふ！！)シュビドゥバ メロメロ
Flying, shubiduba, head over heels,
みんな(ふ！！)集まれ ゾロゾロ
Everyone gather, streaming in,
こん^^chu☆ chu☆
Con^^chu☆ chu☆
パヤパヤパヤ パ
Paya paya paya pa!
ギラギラギラ ファ ファ
Glare glare glare fa fa!
ギラギラギラ ファ
Glare glare glare fa!
ご注文のスーパーアイドル準備中 16:30に到着予定
[Preparing your super idol. Estimated arrival at 16:30]
準備完了
[Preparation Complete]
配達中 >
[Delivering >]
東京ガーデンシアター TOKYO GARDEN THEATER
[Tokyo Garden Theater]
あ～あ 朝、目が覚めたら 枕の側に
Ah... When I wake up in the morning, by my pillow...
帯付きの5000兆 添えられてたらいいな
...I hope 5,000 trillion yen is waiting there.
あ～あ 3食 昼寝あり できることなら
Ah... Three meals a day with naps, if possible,
おやつ付き 大企業 コングラッチュ☆社長出勤
with snacks at a big corp: Congratulate☆ President at work!
生まれてきた今日に おめでとっ！
Congratulations on the day we were born!
今日、明日、明後日 毎日誰かの誕生日
Today, tomorrow, or later—every day's someone's birthday!
祝福の鈴 鳴らしたら 笑顔咲け！
Ring the bells of blessing and let smiles bloom!
月曜はおやすみ 水曜もなしで 不労所得 毎日ボーナス～
Mondays off, no Wednesdays either, unearned daily bonuses!
そうだ！明日も何かの祝日用にしよう！ そうしようっ！
That's it! Let's make tomorrow a holiday too! Let's do that!
異世界からやってきた 憧れと希望胸に この場所
Coming from another world with dreams and hope in our hearts,
歌って踊って 全世界 届けましょう 届けましょう
let's sing and dance and reach the whole world!
あ～あ 朝、起きるだけで 褒められたいな
Ah... Just waking up in the morning deserves praise!
誰にもみせてない才能 そそろ出してやるか
Time to finally show off my hidden talent, right?
あ～ 多分いる 神様 聞こえてますか？
Ah... You're probably out there, God, can you hear me?
願ってる この願い すべてを叶えてくれー！
Grant every single one of my heartfelt wishes!
お礼はこの歌でって事でいいよね 有り難っ！
Expressing my thanks with this song is fine, right? Thanks!
今日、明日、明後日 毎日誰かの誕生日
Today, tomorrow, or later—every day's someone's birthday!
祝福の鈴 鳴らしたら 笑顔咲け！
Ring the bells of blessing and let smiles bloom!
ロケットを作って どこまでもいこう 宇宙旅行 月すら超えて
Let's build a rocket and go anywhere, space travel past the moon!
そうだ！明日も誰かのお祝いをしよう！ そうしようっ！
That's it! Let's celebrate someone tomorrow too! Let's do that!
みんなみんな おめでとっ！
Congratulations to everyone, everyone!
全力で振り切れ
Swing with all your might!
全開で行こう
Go full throttle!
思いっきりやればなんとかなるよ
If you do your best, it'll somehow work out!
高速縦移動
High-speed vertical movement!
突っ走っていい
Just rushing forward is fine!
ただ駆け抜けていこうよね
Let's just run through it all!
全力で振り切れ
Swing with all your might!
全開で行こう
Go full throttle!
みんなも一緒に
Everyone together too!
よしゃよしゃよしゃよしゃ！
Let's go, let's go!
野菜たくさんとお菓子そろえて準備はOK？
Veggies and sweets ready, is prep okay?
楽しむだけね全力全開で行こう
Just enjoy it and go full throttle!
やっぱり君に絶対会いたいよね
After all, I definitely want to see you!
朝早く起きて出かけよう
Wake up early and head out!
生きていればなんとかなるよ
If you're alive, things will work out!
高速縦移動
High-speed vertical movement!
ただ駆け抜けていこうよね
Let's just run through it all!
たくさんの人に愛し合い（ちゅっちゅっ！）
Loving each other among so many people (Chu chu!)
大好きなみんなに愛し合い（ちゅっちゅっ！）
Loving all my dearest people (Chu chu!)
そこで笑うんだ
That's where we smile!
ハイパーエナジー！
Hyper energy!
よしゃよしゃよしゃよしゃ！
Let's go, let's go!
野菜たくさんとお菓子そろえて準備はOK？
Veggies and sweets ready, is prep okay?
楽しむだけね全力全開で行こう
Just enjoy it and go full throttle!
やっぱり君に絶対会いたいよね
After all, I definitely want to see you!
朝早く起きて出かけよう
Wake up early and head out!
生きていればなんとかなるよ
If you're alive, things will work out!
誰のことも向けたくないな 怒った声で
I don't want to turn an angry voice at anyone!
あっという間にちゃんとトイレ行ってくるね
I'll be right back from using the restroom in a flash!
今すぐ君に会いに行くね
I'm coming to see you right now!
ばかみんなが声出してくれないと ベネトイレから帰ってこないからよー！
If you guys don't cheer, Vene won't come back from the restroom!
せーの！あしゅしゅ！
Ready, set! Ashushu!
生まれてきた今日に おめでとっ！
Congratulations on the day we were born!
今日、明日、明後日 毎日誰かの誕生日
Today, tomorrow, or later—every day's someone's birthday!
祝福の鈴 鳴らしたら 笑顔咲け！
Ring the bells of blessing and let smiles bloom!
月曜はおやすみ 水曜もなしで 不労所得 毎日ボーナス～
Mondays off, no Wednesdays either, unearned daily bonuses!
そうだ！明日も何かの祝日用にしよう！ そうしようっ！
That's it! Let's make tomorrow a holiday too! Let's do that!
みんなみんな おめでとっ！
Congratulations to everyone, everyone!
みなさん本当にありがとうございます！
Thank you all so very much!
よしゃよしゃよしゃよしゃ！
Let's go, let's go!
野菜たくさんとお菓子そろえて準備はOK？
Veggies and sweets ready, is prep okay?
楽しむだけね全力全開で行こう
Just enjoy it and go full throttle!
やっぱり君に絶対会いたいよね
After all, I definitely want to see you!
朝早く起きて出かけよう
Wake up early and head out!
生きていればなんとかなるよ
If you're alive, things will work out!
高速縦移動
High-speed vertical movement!
ただ駆け抜けていこうよね
Let's just run through it all!
全力で振り切れ全開で行こう
Swing with all your might, go full throttle!
ハイパーエナジー！
Hyper energy!
次も次の曲でぇ…！
And for our next song...!
ずっとからからに乾いているんだ まだまだ夏は終われない
We've been parched all this long, summer still isn't over yet.
みんなの夏曲で盛り上がっていくぞ！
We're going to get hyped up with everyone's summer songs!
涙見せたくなくて
Not wanting to show my tears,
手で積み上げた頬杖
resting my cheek on my hand,
何もまだ青は残しているかな
I wonder if any blue is still left behind.
寝込んだ教科書の嫌なこともいまだに
Even now, the unpleasant things from the textbooks I fell asleep over
忘れさせてくれないな 寂しくさ
won't let me forget, how lonely it is.
しわっとさあ溢れた
With a fizz, it overflowed,
胸が教えてくれる
my heart tells me.
僕らはこの夏を眩しく駆け抜けるんだ まだまだ夏は終われない
We'll dash dazzlingly through this summer, summer still isn't over yet!
パッパッパッ 手足でほら パッパッパッ 跳ねてるから
Pa-pa-pa, with our hands and feet, look, pa-pa-pa, we're bouncing around!
だらだら布団の中でもいいけど
It's fine to be lazy in futon,
体が熱くてもしょうがない
even if my body is burning up, it can't be helped.
昨日なんどの映画みたいに
Just like yesterday's movie over and over again,
寝込んだ今日も沈みに引っかかったあの影も
Even today when I stayed in bed, that shadow caught in the depression
青いまま過ぎる前に何て願ってた
what was I wishing for before it passes by while still blue?
見切りれなかった日も散々なのよ今なら
Even days I couldn't give up on were miserable, but now
これもアクセントって思えた
I can think of this as an accent too.
ひらっとさ響かせた
Fluttering, it echoed,
心の言葉星に祈って
praying to the stars for the words in my heart.
あの日の二人には何が言えるかな
What can I say to the two of us from that day?
みんなの選手 今日ここで今手でいっぱい見せてください
Everyone's players, please show me plenty with your hands right here and now!
ずっとからからに仕込んでいるんだ 僕ら心が動くことも
We've been packing it in parched all along, even our hearts moving.
あと戻りなんてできやしないから
Because we can't turn back anymore,
まっすぐ
straight ahead!
僕らはドキドキにいつだって踊らされて朝を迎いちゃうような
We're always made to dance by the excitement, as if welcoming the morning,
そんな毎日にしてずっとちっぽけなまままでいた
making every day like that, staying tiny all along.
すぐのねはまだ止まらない
My immediate tears still won't stop.
パッパッパッ 弾けてさぁ パッパッパッ 走ってさぁ
Pa-pa-pa, bursting, pa-pa-pa, running,
たたたたんだある声もやもやもせくのもふせて
stumbling, voices, hazy feelings, hiding the impatience.
君もそのままで描いていて
You too, keep drawing just as you are.
ずっと夜桜ピンクの花無用に僕ら息を切らし
Always like cherry blossom pink flowers breathlessly running out,
遊びのモード全開さ咲かせてみたいな
play mode wide open, I want to make it bloom.
汗ばむこともカラカモ追い越すのきっとそれくらいでいいの
Sweating it out, overtaking the thirst, surely that's enough.
今は何をもたもくずに続けて
Now, without hesitating, continuing,
さぁ行こうハイハイハイハイ
now let's go, hi, hi, hi, hi!
というわけで始まりました！
And so, it has begun!
ももすずねねファーストライブ「たなか」！
Momosuzu Nene's 1st Live 'Tanaka'!
超開会！
Super opening!
じゃあまずねねの自己紹介をさせていただきたいと思います！
Now first, if you'll allow me to introduce myself!
ねねがみんなの心のって言ったら
When Nene says 'everyone's heart',
みんななんて返すんだっけ？
what do you guys reply with?
その通りよくできました！じゃあいくよ！
Spot on, well done! Alright, here we go!
ホロライブネポラボのね！みんなの心の！
Hololive's Nepolabo's Ne! Everyone's heart's!
待ちに待ったファーストライブ！
Long-awaited 1st Live!
今回のテーマは楽しさ最大出力！をテーマにねねがみんなと一緒に超開化していくっていうライブにしていきたいと思ってます！
This time's theme is maximum fun output! Nene wants to make this a live where we all open up together!
普通のライブと違って、みんなが参加してめちゃくちゃ楽しめるようにね、いっぱいワクワクとかドキドキを持ってきたから、みんな楽しみにしててね！
Unlike a regular live, since everyone participates and can enjoy it like crazy, I brought lots of excitement and thrills, so look forward to it!
そしてねねのファーストアルバム「Pekochu Story」、みんな聞いてくれた？
And everyone, have you listened to Nene's 1st album 'Pekochu Story'?
いいね もうなんかタオルがちょっと汗ばんでる人がいるくない？
Goodness, aren't there some people whose towels are already a bit sweaty?
みんな、どの曲が好きだった？ せーの！
Everyone, which song did you like best? Ready, go!
おーおーおー ちょっと待って、そっちの人
Oh, oh, oh... Wait a second, you guys over there—
な、な、なに、なに、何が好き？
Wh-wh-what, what, what do you like?
全部？ 全部！ こっち、こっちの人は？
Everything? Everything! How about you guys over here?
全部、全部か！ ねえねも全部好きでーす！
Everything, everything? Nene loves everything too!
ありがとう！ そして今回はガールズバンドの生演奏でお届けしていきます！ご紹介をさせてください！
Thank you! And this time, we're delivering the performance with a live girls' band! Please let me introduce them!
キーボードでバンドマスターのシーリィホさん！
On keyboard and band master, Cley-Ho!
そしてギターのリーツマ・リオンさん！
And on guitar, Reatsuma Marion!
そしてベースのアイビー・ベイダーさん！
And on bass, Ivy Bader!
ドラムのパンダ・ナナコさんです！
And on drums, Panda Nanako!
はい、そしてちょっとね配信の方にも触れていきたいと思うんですけど、みんなコメントいっぱいありがとう！このへんにね あの配信の人が見ているカメラがあるの。えーい！みなさんいっぱいスクショ撮ってね！
Yes, and I'd also like to touch on the stream. Thank you all so much for all the comments! There's a camera right around here for the viewers watching the stream. Yay! Everyone, take lots of screenshots!
そして今回のライブの感想とかはね、全部ハッシュタグ もも、あ、違う、ちゃん、ね、ハッシュタグねね超会歌でたくさんポストしてください！
And please post your thoughts on this live using the hashtag #NeneChouKaika!
そして今YouTubeそしてTikTokでご覧の方は次の曲まで聴けるので、まだまだ一緒に盛り上がりたーいって人は概要欄から配信サイトへGOしてください！
And for those watching on YouTube and TikTok, you can listen up to the next song, so if you want to keep getting hyped up together, go to the streaming site via the description box!
さあみんな、始まる前からギラファンねね症出そうしてたけど、まだライブ始まってたった2曲だからね！ってことで次の曲いこうかな！次は少ししっとりめの曲から聴いてください。
Now everyone, you were already getting all hyped up even before it started, but the live has only just begun after two songs! So let's move on to the next song! Next, please listen to a slightly more sentimental song.
覚えてるかな？
Do you remember?
桜色に染まった
Dyed in cherry blossom pink,
帰り道の途中
along the way home.
流れてくる春のふきだまりを歩きながら
Walking through drifts of spring breeze,
少し背伸びしていた 変わらない距離感を
standing on my tiptoes, wishing to close
本当は縮めたくて
the unchanging distance between us.
言えなくて
Unable to say it,
言わなくて
choosing not to say it,
「またね」じゃ足りないよ
"See you later" isn't enough.
いつかまた会えるかな？
Will we meet again someday?
君と何回だって 何回だって 笑い合えた春の日
The spring days we laughed together, over and over,
風に舞ってふわり消えた それでも忘れない
danced on the wind and faded away, yet I won't forget.
ほぐれた手と手 離れていく 言葉を探していた
Hands untangling and pulling apart, as I searched for words.
淡く揺れてとけた想い それでも忘れない
Feelings that gently swayed and melted away, yet I won't forget.
さようならではなく ありがとう
Not goodbye, but thank you.
言葉をつなげて
Piecing words together,
胸の奥にしまった
I tucked them deep inside my heart.
あどけない気持ち
Innocent feelings,
本当は伝えたくて
truly wanting to convey them.
届けたい 届かない
Wanting to reach you, yet out of reach,
「またね」じゃ足りないけど
"See you later" isn't enough, but
いつかまた会えるかな？
will we meet again someday?
君と何回だって 何回だって 見上げた空の色も
The color of the sky we looked up at together, over and over,
風に乗ってヒラリ飛んだ 花びらの色も
and the color of petals fluttering on the wind.
これから描く未来地図 魔法みたいに染めて
Dyeing the future map we'll draw from now on like magic—
きっとそこに君はいない 明日だとしても
even if tomorrow you won't be there.
今も色褪せない記憶 写真みたいに色付いて
Memories that still haven't faded, colorful like photos,
ずーっとずーっと思い出達 春の匂いがした
all our memories together always smelled of spring.
君と何回だって 何回だって 笑い合えた春の日
The spring days we laughed together, over and over,
風に舞ってふわり消えた それでも忘れない
danced on the wind and faded away, yet I won't forget.
ほぐれた手と手 離れていく 言葉を探していた
Hands untangling and pulling apart, as I searched for words.
淡く揺れてとけた想い それでも忘れない
Feelings that gently swayed and melted away, yet I won't forget.
さようならではなく ありがとう
Not goodbye, but thank you.
花びらの色も
The color of the petals too,
これから描く未来地図
The future map we'll draw from now on
魔法みたいに染めて
Dyed like magic,
きっとそこに君はいない
Surely you won't be there,
明日だとしても
Even if it's tomorrow.
今も今も
Now too, now too,
あせない記憶
Unfading memories.
写真みたいに色付いて
Colored like a photograph,
ずっとずっと想い出達
Memories on and on,
ハーモニー響いた
Harmonizing into the night.
君となんだって何だって
Whatever it was with you,
笑い合えた春の日
The spring days we shared a laugh.
君となんだって何だって
Whatever it was with you,
なんだって
Whatever it was...
笑い合えた春の日
The spring days we shared a laugh,
風に揺れてふわり消えた
Fluttering in the wind and fading away.
それでも忘れない
Even so, I won't forget.
ほどけた手と手離れてゆく
Hands parting ways that were once clasped,
言葉を探していた
I was searching for words.
淡く揺れてとけた想い
Faintly swaying and dissolving feelings,
それでも忘れない
Even so, I won't forget.
さよならじゃなくて
Not a goodbye, but...
ありがとう
Thank you.
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせてよ
Let the newborn heartbeat resonate!